<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ReadMoreTextView</string>
    <string name="dummy_text">Android is a mobile operating system developed by Google, based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software and designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. In addition, Google has further developed Android TV for televisions, Android Auto for cars, and Wear OS for wrist watches, each with a specialized user interface. Variants of Android are also used on game consoles, digital cameras, PCs and other electronics.  Initially developed by Android Inc., which Google bought in 2005, Android was unveiled in 2007, with the first commercial Android device launched in September 2008. The operating system has since gone through multiple major releases, with the current version being 8.1 \"Oreo\", released in December 2017. The core Android source code is known as Android Open Source Project (AOSP), and is primarily licensed under the Apache License.</string>
    <string name="google">Google LLC The letters of \"Google\" are each purely colored (from left to right) in blue, red, yellow, blue, green, and red. Google\'s logo since 2015 Googleplex-Patio-Aug-2014.JPG Google\'s headquarters, the Googleplex, in August 2014 Formerly called Google Inc. (1998–2017) Type Subsidiary Industry\t Internet Software Computer hardware Founded\tSeptember 4, 1998; 19 years ago in Menlo Park, California, U.S.[1][2] Founders\t Larry Page Sergey Brin Headquarters\tGoogleplex, Mountain View, California, U.S.[3] Area served Worldwide Key people Sundar Pichai (CEO) Ruth Porat (CFO) Products\tList of Google products Number of employees 85,050[4] (Q1 2018) Parent\tAlphabet Inc. (2015–present) Subsidiaries\tList of subsidiaries Website\tgoogle.com Google LLC[5] is an American multinational technology company that specializes in Internet-related services and products, which include online advertising technologies, search engine, cloud computing, software, and hardware. Google was founded in 1998 by Larry Page and Sergey Brin while they were Ph.D. students at Stanford University, California. Together, they own about 14 percent of its shares and control 56 percent of the stockholder voting power through supervoting stock.</string>
    <string name="apple"><![CDATA[Apple Inc. Apple logo black.svg Aerial view of Apple Park dllu.jpg Apple Park in Cupertino, California, 2018 Formerly called Apple Computer Company (1976–1977) Apple Computer, Inc. (1977–2007) Type Public Traded as\t NASDAQ: AAPL NASDAQ-100 component DJIA component S&P 100 component S&P 500 component ISIN\tUS0378331005 Industry\t Computer hardware Computer software Consumer electronics Digital distribution Semiconductors Fabless silicon design Corporate venture capital Founded\tApril 1, 1976; 42 years ago Founders\t Steve Jobs Steve Wozniak Ronald Wayne Headquarters\tApple Park, 1 Apple Park Way, Cupertino, California, U.S. Number of locations 500 retail stores (2018) Area served Worldwide Key people Arthur D. Levinson (Chairman) Tim Cook (CEO) Luca Maestri (CFO) Jeff Williams (COO) Jony Ive (CDO) Products\t Macintosh iPod iPhone iPad Apple Watch Apple TV HomePod macOS iOS watchOS tvOS iLife iWork Final Cut Pro Logic Pro Services\t Apple Pay Apple Store iTunes Store App Store Mac App Store iBooks Store iCloud Apple Music Revenue\tIncrease US$229.234 billion[1] (2017) Operating income Increase US$61.344 billion[1] (2017) Net income Increase US$48.351 billion[1] (2017) Total assets\tIncrease US$375.319 billion[1] (2017) Total equity\tIncrease US$134.047 billion[1] (2017) Number of employees 123,000[1] (2017) Subsidiaries\t Shazam Texture FileMaker Inc. Anobit Braeburn Capital Beats Electronics Beddit Apple Energy, LLC Apple Sales International[2] Apple Worldwide Video[3] Website\tapple.com Apple Inc. is an American multinational technology company headquartered in Cupertino, California, that designs, develops, and sells consumer electronics, computer software, and online services. The company\'s hardware products include the iPhone smartphone, the iPad tablet computer, the Mac personal computer, the iPod portable media player, the Apple Watch smartwatch, the Apple TV digital media player, and the HomePod smart speaker.]]></string>
    <string name="blackberry">BlackBerry is a line of smartphones, tablets, and services originally designed and marketed by Canadian company BlackBerry Limited (formerly known as Research In Motion, or RIM).[1] These are currently designed, manufactured, and marketed by TCL Communication (under the brand of BlackBerry Mobile), BB Merah Putih, and Optiemus for the global, Indonesian, and Indian markets (respectively) using the BlackBerry brand under license.</string>
</resources>
